Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. General Subject files
  - Subseries 2. Central Arizona Project
    - Central Arizona Project (S. 75) Committee Report #832 - 81st Congress, 1st Session, Accession no. M0223 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - S.75, Accession no. M0223 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - S. 75, Central Arizona Project, Committee Reports and Various Statistics and Documents, Accession no. M0223 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Comments and Questions Addressed by the House Committee on Public Lands to the Secretary of the Interior and the Director of the Bureau of the Budget re: S. 75, 81st Congress, 1st Session., Accession no. M0223 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - S. 75, Comments on Answers Submitted by the Department of the Interior to Questions Asked by the-House Committee on Public's Lands, Central Arizona Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - S. 75, Proposed Amendments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Reports on Central Arizona Project Bills, Litigation Resolutions and Related Subjects, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Central Arizona Project - Proposed Amendments, Reports, H.R. 1500, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 1500, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Central Arizona Project - Pertinent Quotations from Report of the President's Water Resources Policy Commission, Vol. I, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 1500, Comments by M. J. Dowd, Technical Adviser, Colorado River Board of California; Factors Affecting Economy of Central Arizona, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 2, Excerpts from Central Arizona Project Hearings, 1949, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 3, Excerpts from Central Arizona Project, 1947 - 1964 Congressional Hearings, Accession no. M0223 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 4, Questions and Discussions During Field Hearings of the House Irrigation and Reclamation Subcommittee, 11/9/64, Accession no. M0223 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Material for Senator Downey re: S. 75, 6/14/49, Accession no. M0223 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda and Comments on S. 75 as Passed by the Senate to Authorize the Central Arizona Project, with Supplemental Data, Accession no. M0223 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Comments on Questions Addressed by the House Committee on Public Lands to the Secretary of the Interior and the Director of the Bureau of the Budget re: S. 75, 81st Congress, 1st Session; miscellaneous material, Accession no. M0223 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Water...Water...Water - Cartoons by Gaylord Pierce on the Central Arizona Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Comments on S. 75 ( as passed by the Senate) to Authorize the Central Arizona Project with Supplemental Data, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft - Comparison of Alternative Diversion Routes - Central Arizona Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous memoranda - Frank Cases Distinguished, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Brief on Legal Aspects of H. R. 1500 - 1501, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Data Concerning S. 75 and H.R. 1500., Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Central Arizona and Colorado River Proposed Legislation, 80th - 82nd Congress, Accession no. M0223 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - S. 75 - Folder of miscellaneous material and releases, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Boulder Canyon Project Appropriation Laws and Administration Interpretations, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Colorado River Board Hearings - notes, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Perliminary Report on Bridge Canyon Power Development, 3/42, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Senate Debates on S. 75, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Information on S. 75, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Information on S. 75, Accession no. M0223 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 5. 75, 81st Congress - Bill as Reported, Senate Committee Report, Printed Amendments, Bill as Passed by Senate, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - S. 75, 81st Congress - Senate Debates, 2/6-2l/50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Comments on Authorization for Suit Contained in Sec. 12 and 13 of S. 75 (H.R. 1500), 82nd Congress, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - S. 75 - Amendments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Committee Print, 10/2/51, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Statement Before the Subcommittee on Irrigation and Reclamation of the Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, House of Representatives, by Floyd L. Goss, Accession no. M0223 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 3. Colorado River
    - Sub-subseries 1. Colorado River Controversy
      - Index to Exhibits - California, Set #3, Accession no. M0223 (Box 25)
      - Index to Exhibits - Arizona, Set #3, Accession no. M0223 (Box 26)
      - Index to Exhibits - Nevada, New Mexico, Utah, Set #12, Accession no. M0223 (Box 27)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California Exhibits #1 - Appropriative Rights, Accession no. M0223 (Box 28)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Boulder Canyon Project Act and Bridge Canyon Development, Accession no. M0223 (Box 29)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - California Cases and Colorado River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 30)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Colorado River Compact - Compacts Generally, Accession no. M0223 (Box 31)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Consumptive Use, Accession no. M0223 (Box 32)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Contracts and Desert Land Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 33)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Evidence and Findings, Accession no. M0223 (Box 34)
      - Gila River System - Ground water, Accession no. M0223 (Box 34)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Imperial Irrigation District, Indians, International Law and Interstate Litigation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 35)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Issues, Questions, Studies, Accession no. M0223 (Box 36)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Issues, Questions, Studies, Accession no. M0223 (Box 37)
      - Issues, questions, studies #3, Accession no. M0223 (Box 37)
      - Colorado River Controversy -Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0223 (Box 38)
        - Judicial Controversy
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Master, Metropolitan Water District, Mexican Water Treaty, Mexico, Nevada and Parties, Accession no. M0223 (Box 39)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Procedure - Pre-trial, Accession no. M0223 (Box 40)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Reclamation Act of 1902, Reservoir (Evaporption) Losses, Salvage Water, Statuatory Compact, Statutory Interpretation, Third Party Beneficiary Treaties, United States and Upper Basin, Accession no. M0223 (Box 41)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Water Rights, Accession no. M0223 (Box 42)
      - Colorado River Controversy - Arizona vs. California - Water Supply, Accession no. M0223 (Box 43)
      - Utah Exhibits, Vol. 1 - Set #5, Accession no. M0223 (Box 44)
      - Utah Exhibits, Vol. 2 - Set #5, Accession no. M0223 (Box 44)
      - Arizona Case as Proved under her Pleadings, Accession no. M0223 (Box 45)
      - Nevada Exhibits - Colorado River Case, Set #12, Accession no. M0223 (Box 46)
      - Arizona vs. California - Decree, Accession no. M0223 (Box 47)
      - The Western Web, 1947 - 1952 by John U. Terrell, Accession no. M0223 (Box 48)
      - The Western Web, Indexes and Vol. 1, Accession no. M0223 (Box 49)
      - The Western Web, Vol. 2, Accession no. M0223 (Box 50)
      - The Western Web, Vol. 3, Accession no. M0223 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous notes in folder, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Limitation Act Issue, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Hearings Before the Special Master, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Report of W. S. Norviel, Colorado River Commissioner, State of Arizona, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Arizona vs. California - Chronological Histories of the Development of Four Major Water Supplies in the United States, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Arizona vs. California - U. S. Supreme Court - Basic Information About California Agencies, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda and Opinions - Colorado River Controversy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Extracts from Arizona vs. California Cases 283, 292 and 298, U.S. Reports (2 copies), Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Extracts from Colorado River Supreme Court Litigation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Data on H.J. 226, Accession no. M0223 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - The Colorado River Controversy is Justiciable Now without Authorization of the Central Arizona Project, 4/11/50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 0)
      - Questions Arising in Connection with the Proposal that the U.S. Initiate an Action in the Supreme Court to Determine - the Colorado River Controversy, 4/13/50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 0)
      - Explanation of Terms in the Colorado River Controversy Between Arizona and California by Hon. Charles B. Ward, 8/1/29, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Comments on the Authorization for Suit Contained in Sections 12 and 13 of S. 75, 81st Congress, 4/17/50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Index - Record of Arizona vs. California, 283 U.S. 423 (1931), Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Index - Record of Arizona vs. California, 292 U.S. 341 (1934), Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Decrees in the Interstate Water Suits - Draft of paper given before the Wyoming Bar Association 10/18-19/46 by W. J. Wehrli, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - The Colorado River Controversy, by James H. Howard, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Southern California's Colorado River Water Supply in the Balance, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - The Colorado River Controversy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Appeal from the General Land Office - Application for private exchange of Arizona lands held for rejection, 12/26/47, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Comments on the Arizona-California Controversy Relating to the Waters of the Colorado River, by Rex Hardy, 4/1/47, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - California's Comments on an Arizona Memorandum entitled "History and Status of the Colorado River Controversy" by Rex Hardy, James H. Howard, Arvin B. Shaw, Jr., Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Memoranda submitted to Mr. Bell at the White House, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - The Colorado River Controversy is Justiciable Now without Authorization of the Central Arizona Project, draft of 4/1/51, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - The Arizona Enabling Act Does Not Affect the Justiciability or the Merits of the Colorado River Controversy, 4/2/51, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Questions Arising in Connection with the Proposal that the U.S. Initiate an Action in the Supreme Court to Determine - the Colorado River Controversy, draft of 4/4/51, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - California's Stake in the Colorado River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - The Present Delicate and Complicated Question - The Colorado River Controversy, by Stanley Duff Hooper, 4/53, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - TL mimeo, 7/19/54, from George I Haight re: Arizona vs. California et. al., 10/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Colorado River Deficits - A Paper Presented at a Meeting of the Sacramento Section, American Society of Civil Engineers, in Sacramento, California by Raymond A.Hill, 12/7/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Arizona vs. California - List of Memoranda Prepared by Members of and Circulated to the Legal Committee, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Library of' Congress Legislative Reference Service '- Protection of Present and Future Diversions in Construction of Flood Control and Power Projects on Navigable Rivers, 2/25/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Index to Oral Arguments on the Joinder Motion Held at Phoenix, Arizona, 4/12-15/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - The Colorado River Controversy: Federal Legislation, 5/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Reader's Digest Reprints:"What Price Too Much Food?" by Gaynor Maddox, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Memoranda, Extracts, etc., Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Arizona vs. California et. al. - Statement of Issues (submitted by the California Defendants), 3/31/56, Accession no. M0223 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Folder of notes re: Arizona vs. California Water Supply, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Arizona vs. California - the Colorado RiverControversy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Water Supply of the Lower Colorado River Basin - Extracts from Briefs and Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law Submitted 4/1/59 to the Hon. Simon H. Rifkin, Special Master, by the California Defendants and Excerpts from the Evidence, Arizona vs. California, 10/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - TL carbon, 5/29/59, Bryant W. Jones, Thaddeus G. Baker and J.D. Mansfield to Stanley Mosk re: Amicus Curiae Brief, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, l959, #9 Orig., 6/30/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, 1959, #9 Orig., Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law proposed by the United States of America., Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, 1959, #9 Orig., Reply Brief for the United States of America, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Arizona vs. California - California Offer of Proof, 8/17/60, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, 1960, #9 Orig., Opening Brief for Arizona, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, 1960, #9 Orig., Brief Support of Exceptions of the United States Intervener, to the Special Master's Report and Recommended Decree, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - TLS, 1/27/61, Charles E. Corker to Gilmore Tillman re: Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - TL xerox, 12/29/61, Robert Kennedy to Secretary of Interior re: Excess Land Limitations, Accession no. M0223 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries 2. General
      - Report of the Water Planning Committee, Part III, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Report of the Federal Power Commission, pgs. 43 - 50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Transactions of the Commonwealth Club, Vol. XVII #11, San Francisco 12/22 - Address by Secretary Herbert Hoover, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Mimeo - Address of Hon. Herbert Hoover before the Commonwealth Club of California at a Luncheon given at the Palace Hotel, San Francisco, Friday, December 1, 1922, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Compilation of Extracts from Congressional Debates on 4th Swing-Johnson Bill, 70th Congress, 2nd Session (1928), Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River Basin Committee Report on Water Supply of the Colorado River and Allied Matters by R. J. Tipton, Denver, Colorado, 7/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Reclamation Project Act - 1939, Amendments - 81st Congress, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Colorado River under conditions of ultimate development - question and answers, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Comprehensive Report in Development of Water Resources of the Colorado River Basin - 6/6/46, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - States' Comments on'Colorado River Comprehensive Report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Use of Water in Lower Basin - Colorado River and Tributaries, Accession no. M0223; 2 pgs. photocopy (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Opinions of A. E. Chandler re: Colorado River Matters, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Opinions of A. E. Chandler re: Colorado River Matters, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Land Limitation Legislation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Compilation of Colorado River Material by Rex Hardy, 4/1/48, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Congressional Tour of California's Colorado River Projects - copy of photographs for Hon. Norris Poulson, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Colorado River Flood Protection Works of Imperial Irrigation District - History and Cost, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Historical Chronology of Colorado River Development, Vol. 1, 1867 - 1964, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Congressional Record, 6/26/30, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Historical material - Arizona, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Memorandum concerning research work in connection with Colorado River problems, Accession no. M0223 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Sub-subseries 3. Boulder Canyon Project
      - Issues, Questions, Studies, Legislative History and Various Legislation, Boulder Canyon Project, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 58)
      - Legislative History, Boulder Canyon Project Act, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 59)
      - List of Exhibits, Boulder Canyon Project Act, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 60)
      - 3 pgs. miscellaneous draft notes for power contracts, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Financial Operation Table - Boulder Canyon, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Table - Allocation of Firm Energy - -Boulder Canyon, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Historical Cost to Southern California Edison Co. for' Operating and Maintaining the Reservoirs, Dams, Tunnels, Flow Lines, Pen Stocks, Tailraces, Power Plant and Miscell?neous Buildings, Employee Cottages, Roads and Other Properties in the Company's Big Creek Project with Proportionate Cost of Supervision and Engineering Therefor, but Exclusive of Costs for Permits, Production Rents, Operating and Maintaining Generating and Transmission Machinery and Equipment, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Legislative History of Section 4(a) - Boulder Canyon Project - 70th Congress, original, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Contract to Contruct 3rd Circuit and Take Additional Boulder Dam Energy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Contract to Construct 3rd Circuit and Take Additional Boulder' Dam Energy Under Existing Conditions, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Legislative History of Section 4(a) of the Boulder Canyon Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Rate which Public and Private Corporations Can Afford to Pay for Power at Boulder Canyon and Rate which will Produce Sufficient Revenue to Repay Cost of Boulder Canyon Dam and Power Plant in 50 Years with Interest, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - House Hearings, Boulder Dam - 5/30, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Boulder Canyon Project - Contract for Lease of Power Privileges, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Boulder Canyon Project - Contract for Delivery of Water, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - All American Canal-- Draft of Contract for Repayment, 10/3/31, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - General Regulations: Leases and Contracts for Hoover Dam Power, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Story of Hoover Dam, Vols. 1 - 4, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Cooperative Contract for Construction and Operation of Parker Dam - original, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Hoover Dam - booklet, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Cooperative Contract for Construction and Operation of Parker Dam, Accession no. M0223 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Statement Prepared for the Convenience of and Use by Arizona's Representatives at the Oral Hearing to be Held on December 17, 1934, Before the Secretary of the Interior re: Proposed Contract with the State of Arizona Pending before the Secretary of the Interior Providing for the Storage and Delivery of Water from the Boulder Dam Reservoir, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Memorandum Regarding Payments Into Separate Funde_ Under the Boulder Canyon Act - 2/4/36, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes, Alternate Draft - 12/8/37, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - draft of 12/10/37, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Outline of Proposed Boulder Dam Legislation - 12/15/37, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - An Act for the Adjustment of Charges and Rates at Boulder Dam and for Other Purposes - draft of 2/1/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Memorandum Regarding Payments into Separate Fund under the Boulder Canyon Project Act - 2/2/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Outline of Boulder Dam Legislation - 4/12/38, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Agreement with Metropolitan Water District Deferring Payments for Boulder Dam Energy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Contract for Resale of Electrical Energy to be Developed at Boulder Dam Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Memorandum Agreement between the United States National Park Service and United States Bureau of Reclamation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum on Power Possibilities at Dam, by-J. R. Riter, with tabulation of annual amounts of firm and secondary energy available with run-offconditions as of 1938 - 1988, 10/25/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Contract for the Operation of Boulder Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - The United States of America and the City of Los Angeles and its Department of Water and Power, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - City Energy Contract, 2/27/41 - 5/27/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - General Regulations for Generation and Sale of Power in Accordance with the Boulder Canyon Adjustment Act, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Contract for Operation of Boulder Power Plant - the United States of America and the City of Los Angeles and its Department of Water and Power and the Southern California Edison Co., Ltd. - draft of 9/14/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Proposed changes for above - 9/29/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - General Regulations for Generation and Sale of Power in Accordance with the Boulder Canyon Adjustment Act, draft of 10/4/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Use of Boulder Power Plant Generating Units by the Agents as Spinning Reserve - 10/18/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Estimates of Personnel and Allocation of Labor Costs for Operation and Maintenance - Boulder' Canyon Dam, Accession no. M0223 (Box 56, Folder 6)